Patthamawan Iteeyaporn (Nune)

p.iteeyaporn@gmail.com
07444619169

7 St.Mary Graces Court, Cartwright Street, London,

Profile

I am passionate about art and technology, and love to apply my combined knowledge to create art for different types of media. I have over 4 years of experience in the 3D animation industry, with TV animation credits for numerous projects and brands including the LEGO animated shows. I'm a self-motivated individual, experienced in managing my own workflow and working as part of a team to deliver projects on time.

I have recently created a website from scratch to house my portfolio. Please visit nunefolio.co.uk to see some of my previous work.

Experience

SENIOR UX/UI DESIGNER AT BOTNOI CONSULTING, BANGKOK - 2020-PRESENT

- Currently leading a team of UX/UI designers to design a new products.
- In charge of redesigning UX / UI for existing Chat bot software tool using Figma and miro.
- Improved UX design for CMS tool.

UX/UI DESIGNER AT ZANROO, BANGKOK - 2016-2019

- Led the design process, managed business expectations and provided regular progress updates.
- Worked closely with the product owners to improve and design new features and products.
- Created prototype and design UX/UI using Sketch, Adobe XD and Invision Studio.
- Applied Responsive Web Design when turning UI concept into HTML/CSS using SASS and React framework on the projects.
- Built a library of reusable components.

3D ANIMATOR AT M2 ANIMATION, BANGKOK - 2015-2016

- Worked on the 2nd season of Lego's Friends and LEGO City mini-movie.
- Pitched ideas on how the scene is going to look to the animation director before animating the scene using Autodesk Maya.
- Cleaning up animations before the final rendering of the scene.

ANIMATOR AT KYORAKU PICTURES, BANGKOK - 2014-2015

- Created action sequences for both character and vehicle animation for Pachinko game machines in Japan.
- Tested rigs and gave feedback to riggers for improvements.
- Cleaned up motion capture using Motionbuilder program.

JUNIOR ANIMATOR AT VITHITA ANIMATION, BANGKOK - 2012-2014

- Responsible for animating, modelling and texturing everyday objects for a Thai Cartoon TV series.
- Created blend-shapes for characters to achieve believable character movements.

Education

Staffordshire University, BA(hons) Animation, 2008-2011 Kingston College, Graphic Designer, 2006-2008

Skills

Photoshop, Illustrator, Adobe XD, Figma, Miro, Autodesk Maya, HTML, CSS

Hobbies

Drawing, Gaming, Movies, Traveling, Playing Sports, Playing Piano